 export const computers = [
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20internet%20company%20began%20life%20as%20an%20online%20bookstore%20called%20%27Cadabra%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Amazon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"eBay",
"Overstock",
"Shopify"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Moore%27s%20law%20originally%20stated%20that%20the%20number%20of%20transistors%20on%20a%20microprocessor%20chip%20would%20double%20every...",
"correct_answer": "Year",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Four%20Years",
"Two%20Years",
"Eight%20Years"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20AD%20stand%20for%20in%20relation%20to%20Windows%20Operating%20Systems%3F%20",
"correct_answer": "Active%20Directory",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Alternative%20Drive",
"Automated%20Database",
"Active%20Department"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20five%20letter%20word%20is%20the%20motto%20of%20the%20IBM%20Computer%20company%3F",
"correct_answer": "Think",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Click",
"Logic",
"Pixel"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "On%20which%20computer%20hardware%20device%20is%20the%20BIOS%20chip%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Motherboard",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hard%20Disk%20Drive",
"Central%20Processing%20Unit",
"Graphics%20Processing%20Unit"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20languages%20is%20used%20as%20a%20scripting%20language%20in%20the%20Unity%203D%20game%20engine%3F",
"correct_answer": "C%23",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Java",
"C%2B%2B",
"Objective-C"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "All%20of%20the%20following%20programs%20are%20classified%20as%20raster%20graphics%20editors%20EXCEPT%3A",
"correct_answer": "Inkscape",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Paint.NET",
"GIMP",
"Adobe%20Photoshop"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20computer%20OEM%20manufacturer%20Clevo%2C%20known%20for%20its%20Sager%20notebook%20line%2C%20is%20based%20in%20which%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Taiwan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"United%20States",
"Germany",
"China%20%28People%27s%20Republic%20of%29"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Nvidia%27s%20headquarters%20are%20based%20in%20which%20Silicon%20Valley%20city%3F",
"correct_answer": "Santa%20Clara",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Palo%20Alto",
"Cupertino",
"Mountain%20View"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20did%20the%20name%20of%20the%20Tor%20Anonymity%20Network%20orignially%20stand%20for%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Onion%20Router",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Only%20Router",
"The%20Orange%20Router",
"The%20Ominous%20Router"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20first%20commerically%20available%20computer%20processor%3F",
"correct_answer": "Intel%204004",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Intel%20486SX",
"TMS%201000",
"AMD%20AM386"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20given%20to%20Android%204.3%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jelly%20Bean",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Lollipop",
"Nutella",
"Froyo"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20the%20name%20for%20the%20failed%20key%20escrow%20device%20introduced%20by%20the%20National%20Security%20Agency%20in%201993%3F",
"correct_answer": "Clipper%20Chip",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Enigma%20Machine",
"Skipjack",
"Nautilus"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "On%20which%20day%20did%20the%20World%20Wide%20Web%20go%20online%3F",
"correct_answer": "December%2020%2C%201990",
"incorrect_answers": [
"December%2017%2C%201996",
"November%2012%2C%201990",
"November%2024%2C%201995"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "While%20Apple%20was%20formed%20in%20California%2C%20in%20which%20western%20state%20was%20Microsoft%20founded%3F",
"correct_answer": "New%20Mexico",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Washington",
"Colorado",
"Arizona"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20the%20acronym%20CDN%20stand%20for%20in%20terms%20of%20networking%3F",
"correct_answer": "Content%20Delivery%20Network",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Content%20Distribution%20Network",
"Computational%20Data%20Network",
"Compressed%20Data%20Network"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Generally%2C%20which%20component%20of%20a%20computer%20draws%20the%20most%20power%3F",
"correct_answer": "Video%20Card",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hard%20Drive",
"Processor",
"Power%20Supply"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20cores%20does%20the%20Intel%20i7-6950X%20have%3F",
"correct_answer": "10",
"incorrect_answers": [
"12",
"8",
"4"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20server%20hosting%20industry%20IaaS%20stands%20for...",
"correct_answer": "Infrastructure%20as%20a%20Service",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Internet%20as%20a%20Service",
"Internet%20and%20a%20Server",
"Infrastructure%20as%20a%20Server"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20coding%20language%20was%20the%20%231%20programming%20language%20in%20terms%20of%20usage%20on%20GitHub%20in%202015%3F",
"correct_answer": "JavaScript",
"incorrect_answers": [
"C%23",
"Python",
"PHP"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20default%20theme%20that%20is%20installed%20with%20Windows%20XP%3F",
"correct_answer": "Luna",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Neptune",
"Whistler",
"Bliss"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20programming%20language%20%22Python%22%2C%20which%20of%20these%20statements%20would%20display%20the%20string%20%22Hello%20World%22%20correctly%3F",
"correct_answer": "print%28%22Hello%20World%22%29",
"incorrect_answers": [
"console.log%28%22Hello%20World%22%29",
"echo%20%22Hello%20World%22",
"printf%28%22Hello%20World%22%29"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20HTML%2C%20which%20non-standard%20tag%20used%20to%20be%20be%20used%20to%20make%20elements%20scroll%20across%20the%20viewport%3F",
"correct_answer": "%3Cmarquee%3E%3C%2Fmarquee%3E",
"incorrect_answers": [
"%3Cscroll%3E%3C%2Fscroll%3E",
"%3Cmove%3E%3C%2Fmove%3E",
"%3Cslide%3E%3C%2Fslide%3E"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20CSS%2C%20which%20of%20these%20values%20CANNOT%20be%20used%20with%20the%20%22position%22%20property%3F",
"correct_answer": "center",
"incorrect_answers": [
"static",
"absolute",
"relative"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20correct%20term%20for%20the%20metal%20object%20in%20between%20the%20CPU%20and%20the%20CPU%20fan%20within%20a%20computer%20system%3F",
"correct_answer": "Heat%20Sink",
"incorrect_answers": [
"CPU%20Vent",
"Temperature%20Decipator",
"Heat%20Vent"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20programming%2C%20the%20ternary%20operator%20is%20mostly%20defined%20with%20what%20symbol%28s%29%3F",
"correct_answer": "%3F%3A",
"incorrect_answers": [
"%3F%3F",
"if%20then",
"%3F"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20programming%20languages%20is%20a%20low-level%20language%3F",
"correct_answer": "Assembly",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Python",
"C%23",
"Pascal"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20computing%20terms%2C%20typically%20what%20does%20CLI%20stand%20for%3F",
"correct_answer": "Command%20Line%20Interface",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Common%20Language%20Input",
"Control%20Line%20Interface",
"Common%20Language%20Interface"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20fast%20is%20USB%203.1%20Gen%202%20theoretically%3F",
"correct_answer": "10%20Gb%2Fs",
"incorrect_answers": [
"5%20Gb%2Fs",
"8%20Gb%2Fs",
"1%20Gb%2Fs"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20%22LCD%22%20stand%20for%3F",
"correct_answer": "Liquid%20Crystal%20Display",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Language%20Control%20Design",
"Last%20Common%20Difference",
"Long%20Continuous%20Design"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20operating%20system%20was%20released%20first%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mac%20OS",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Windows",
"Linux",
"OS%2F2"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20a%20personal%20computer%20made%20by%20the%20Japanese%20company%20Fujitsu%3F",
"correct_answer": "FM-7",
"incorrect_answers": [
"PC-9801",
"Xmillennium%20",
"MSX"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": ".rs%20is%20the%20top-level%20domain%20for%20what%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Serbia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Romania",
"Russia",
"Rwanda"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": ".at%20is%20the%20top-level%20domain%20for%20what%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Austria",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Argentina",
"Australia",
"Angola"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20known%20as%20%22the%20brain%22%20of%20the%20Computer%3F",
"correct_answer": "Central%20Processing%20Unit",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Motherboard",
"Graphics%20Processing%20Unit",
"Keyboard"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20the%20term%20GPU%20stand%20for%3F",
"correct_answer": "Graphics%20Processing%20Unit",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Gaming%20Processor%20Unit",
"Graphite%20Producing%20Unit",
"Graphical%20Proprietary%20Unit"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20first%20Android%20version%20specifically%20optimized%20for%20tablets%3F",
"correct_answer": "Honeycomb",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Eclair",
"Froyo",
"Marshmellow"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20people%20was%20NOT%20a%20founder%20of%20Apple%20Inc%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jonathan%20Ive",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Steve%20Jobs",
"Ronald%20Wayne",
"Steve%20Wozniak"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "When%20did%20the%20online%20streaming%20service%20%22Mixer%22%20launch%3F",
"correct_answer": "2016",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2013",
"2009",
"2011"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Laserjet%20and%20inkjet%20printers%20are%20both%20examples%20of%20what%20type%20of%20printer%3F",
"correct_answer": "Non-impact%20printer",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Impact%20printer",
"Daisywheel%20printer",
"Dot%20matrix%20printer"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20the%20term%20MIME%20stand%20for%2C%20in%20regards%20to%20computing%3F",
"correct_answer": "Multipurpose%20Internet%20Mail%20Extensions",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mail%20Internet%20Mail%20Exchange",
"Multipurpose%20Interleave%20Mail%20Exchange",
"Mail%20Interleave%20Method%20Exchange"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20programming%20language%20was%20developed%20by%20Sun%20Microsystems%20in%201995%3F",
"correct_answer": "Java",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Python",
"Solaris%20OS",
"C%2B%2B"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Approximately%20how%20many%20Apple%20I%20personal%20computers%20were%20created%3F",
"correct_answer": "200",
"incorrect_answers": [
"100",
"500",
"1000"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20programming%2C%20what%20do%20you%20call%20functions%20with%20the%20same%20name%20but%20different%20implementations%3F",
"correct_answer": "Overloading",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Overriding",
"Abstracting",
"Inheriting"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20RAID%20stand%20for%3F",
"correct_answer": "Redundant%20Array%20of%20Independent%20Disks",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Rapid%20Access%20for%20Indexed%20Devices",
"Range%20of%20Applications%20with%20Identical%20Designs",
"Randomized%20Abstract%20Identification%20Description"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20teapot%20often%20seen%20in%20many%203D%20modeling%20applications%20is%20called%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Utah%20Teapot",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Pixar%20Teapot",
"3D%20Teapot",
"Tennessee%20Teapot"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20number%20of%20keys%20on%20a%20standard%20Windows%20Keyboard%3F",
"correct_answer": "104",
"incorrect_answers": [
"64",
"94",
"76"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Unix%20Time%20is%20defined%20as%20the%20number%20of%20seconds%20that%20have%20elapsed%20since%20when%3F",
"correct_answer": "Midnight%2C%20January%201%2C%201970",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Midnight%2C%20July%204%2C%201976",
"Midnight%20on%20the%20creator%20of%20Unix%27s%20birthday",
"Midnight%2C%20July%204%2C%201980"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20bits%20make%20up%20the%20significand%20portion%20of%20a%20single%20precision%20floating%20point%20number%3F",
"correct_answer": "23",
"incorrect_answers": [
"8",
"53",
"15"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20the%20%27S%27%20in%20the%20RSA%20encryption%20algorithm%20stand%20for%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shamir",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Secure",
"Schottky",
"Stable"
]
}
]